[Common]
ApplicationName="Event Manager"
InstallFolderPath=%ProgramFiles%\EPSON Software\Event Manager
SilentInstall=-NOLA
Installer=Setup.exe

RunServerOS=0

LastFirmVer=0

PrinterOnline=0

DefaultInstall=1
UpdateOnly=0

LocalInstaller="%AppPath%EventManager"
UpdateName="Event Manager"
UpdateCTI=61

[Japanese]
ApplicationName="Event Manager"

[ApplicationDescription]
Japanese="操作パネルのスキャン機能を実行したときの処理方法を設定します。"
English="This lets you assign any of the scanner buttons to open a scanning program. You can also save the scan settings that frequently used. It makes scanning your projects even quicker."
French="Cette fonction vous permet d'ouvrir un programme de numérisation à l'aide d'une des touches du scanner. Vous pouvez également enregistrer les paramètres de numérisation fréquemment utilisés. La numérisation des projets est alors encore plus rapide."
German="Hiermit können Sie einer beliebigen Scannertaste die Funktion zum Öffnen eines Scanprogramms zuweisen. Sie können auch die am häufigsten genutzten Scaneinstellungen speichern, so dass Scanvorgänge noch schneller werden."
Dutch="Hiermee kunt u een van de knoppen van de scanner gebruiken om een bepaald scanprogramma te openen. Scaninstellingen die u vaak gebruikt, kunt u opslaan. Zo wordt scannen nog gemakkelijker."
Italian="Consente di assegnare un qualsiasi tasto dello scanner per l'apertura di un programma di scansione. È inoltre possibile salvare le impostazioni di scansione usate di frequente. La scansione dei progetti risulta ancora più rapida."
Spanish="Le permite asignar cualquier botón del escáner para que abra un programa de escaneado. También puede guardar los ajustes de escaneado que use con frecuencia. Con él el escaneado es aun más rápido."
Portuguese="Permite-lhe atribuir qualquer tecla do digitalizador para abrir um programa de digitalização. Pode também guardar as definições de digitalização que utiliza frequentemente. Digitalizar os seus projectos torna-se ainda mais rápido."
Turkish="Bu, bir tarama programını açmak için herhangi bir tarayıcı düğmesini atayabilmenizi sağlar. Ayrıca sık kullanılan tarama ayarlarını da kaydedebilirsiniz. Bu durum projelerinizin taranmasını çok daha hızlı hale getirir."
Greek="Αυτό σας επιτρέπει να αντιστοιχίζετε οποιαδήποτε κουμπιά του σαρωτή για να ανοίγετε ένα πρόγραμμα σάρωσης. Επίσης, μπορείτε να αποθηκεύετε τις ρυθμίσεις σάρωσης που χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά. Αυτό καθιστά τις εργασίες σάρωσης ακόμα γρηγορότερες."
Slovenian="Tako lahko tipkam čitalnika dodelite posebne programe. Shranite lahko pogosto uporabljene nastavitve skeniranja. Skeniranje projektov je tako še hitrejše."
Croatian="Ovo Vam omogućava da bilo kojem gumbu skenera pridodijelite funkciju pokretanja programa za skeniranje. Također možete pohraniti često korištene postavke skeniranja. To Vaše skeniranje čini još bržim."
Macedonian="За назначување на копчињата на сканерот за отворање на програма за сканирање. Може и да ги сочувате често користените поставки за сканирање. Со тоа сканирањето станува уште побрзо."
Serbian="Ovo omogućava dodelu bilo kog dugmeta skenera radi otvaranja programa za skeniranje. Uz to možete sačuvati često korišćena podešavanja skenera. Time se ubrzava skeniranje projekata."
Danish="Denne giver dig mulighed for at tildele en hvilken som helst af scannerens knapper til åbning af et scanneprogram. Du kan også gemme hyppigt anvendte scanneindstillinger. Det gør scanningen med dine produkter endnu hurtigere."
Finnish="Tämän avulla voit määrittää minkä tahansa skannerin painikkeen avaamaan skannausohjelmisto. Voit myös tallentaa usein käytetyt skannausasetukset. Tämä tekee projektien skannauksesta entistä nopeamman."
Norwegian="Gjør det mulig å tilordne en skannerknapp for å åpne et skanneprogram. Du kan dessuten lagre de skanneinnstillingene du bruker ofte. Gjør det enda raskere å skanne prosjektene."
Swedish="Gör att du kan ange en skannerknapp som öppnar ett skanningsprogram. Du kan även spara skanningsinställningar som används ofta. Det gör att det går fortare att skanna."
Polish="To pozwala na przypisanie jakiemukolwiek przyciskowi skanera funkcji otwierania programu do skanowania. Można także zapisać ustawienia skanowania, które są często używane. Dzięki temu skanowanie projektów przebiega jeszcze szybciej."
Czech="Umožní vám přiřadit tlačítka skeneru tak, aby jakékoliv z nich otevřelo skenovací program. Můžete také ukládat nastavení skenování, které často používáte. Skenování vašich projektů tak bude ještě rychlejší."
Hungarian="Ennek segítségével a szkenner bármely gombjához hozzárendelhet egy gombot, amellyel megnyílik a szkennelőprogram. Mentheti a gyakran használt szkennelési beállításokat is. Ezzel a szkennelés gyorsabban fog menni."
Slovakian="Umožní vám priradiť tlačidlá skenera tak, aby akékoľvek z nich otvorilo skenovací program. Môžete tiež ukladať nastavenia skenovania, ktoré často používate. Skenovanie vašich projektov tak bude ešte rýchlejšie."
Romanian="Acesta vă permite să atribuiţi unul dintre butoanele scanerului pentru deschiderea unui program de scanare. De asemenea, puteţi salva setările de scanare utilizate frecvent. Scanarea proiectelor devine şi mai rapidă."
Bulgarian="Позволява ви да присвоявате функция за отваряне на програма за сканиране на всеки от бутоните на скенера. Можете също да запаметявате често използвани настройки на сканирането. Прави сканирането на вашите проекти по-бързо."
Latvian="Tā ļauj piešķirt jebkuru skenera pogu skenēšanas dokumenta atvēršanai. Jūs varat arī saglabāt biežāk izmantotos skenēšanas iestatījumus. Tas padara projektu skenēšanu vēl ātrāku."
Lithuanian="Leidžia priskirti bet kurį skaitytuvo mygtuką atidaryti nuskaitymo programą. Taip pat galite įrašyti dažnai naudojamus nuskaitymo parametrus. Taip nuskaitymo projektai tampa spartesni."
Estonian="Sellega saate määrata skannimistarkvara avamiseks mis tahes skanneri nupu. Saate salvestada sageli kasutatud skannimissätted. See lihtsustab veelgi skannimistöid."
Catalan="Així podeu utilitzar qualsevol dels botons de l'escàner per obrir un programa d'escaneig. També podeu desar les configuracions d'escaneig més freqüents. D'aquesta manera, l'escaneig dels vostres projectes serà encara més ràpid."
Russian="Позволяет назначить любую из кнопок сканера, чтобы открывать программу для сканирования. Вы можете также сохранить часто используемые настройки сканирования. Сканирование ваших проектов производится еще быстрее."
Ukrainian="Дає змогу призначати кнопки сканера для відкриття програми сканування. Також можна зберегти найуживаніші настройки сканування. Це допоможе сканувати документи швидше."
Kazakh="Бұл сканер түймелерін ашық сканер бағдарламаға белгілеу болады. Тағы да, қайта-қайта пайдаланған сканер параметрлерін сақтау болады. Осы сіздің жобаларын жылдам сканерлеу мүмкіндігін береді."
Arabic="يتيح لك ذلك تعيين أي من أزرار الماسحة الضوئية لفتح برنامج للمسح الضوئي. كما يمكنك حفظ إعدادات المسح الضوئي الكثير استخدامها. ذلك مما يجعل مسح مشاريعك ضوئيًا أسرع."
Farsi="این نرم افزار به شما امكان می دهد تا هركدام از دكمه های اسكنر را به باز كردن برنامه اسكن اختصاص دهید. همچنین می توانید تنظیمات اسكن كه معمولاً مورد استفاده قرار می دهید را ذخیره نمایید. با این كار اسكن كردن سریعتر می شود."
Korean="스캐너 버튼을 눌렀을 때 실행되는 프로그램을 할당할 수 있는 소프트웨어입니다. 또한, 자주 사용하는 스캔 설정을 저장할 수 있어 스캔 작업을 더 쉽게 할 수 있습니다."
Thai="นี่ทำให้ท่านกำหนดปุ่มใดๆ บนสแกนเนอร์ให้เปิดโปรแกรมสแกน ท่านยังสามารถบันทึกการตั้งค่าสแกนที่ใช้งานบ่อย ทำให้การสแกนโปรเจ็กต์ต่างๆ ของท่านรวดเร็วยิ่งขึ้น"
Chinese="此功能让您指定任意扫描仪按钮来打开一个扫描程序。您还可将经常使用的扫描设置保存下来。这样可让您更为快速地进行扫描。"
Taiwan="這可讓您指派任一個掃描器按鍵來開啟掃描程式。您也可以儲存常用的掃描設定。這樣可讓特殊項目的掃描速度更快。"
HongKong=""
