[Common]
ApplicationName="Yonde!!Koko Personal"
InstallFolderPath=%ProgramFiles%\AiSoft\Yonde
SilentInstall=-sms -NOLA
Installer=Setup.exe

RunServerOS=0

LastFirmVer=0

PrinterOnline=0

DefaultInstall=0
UpdateOnly=0

LocalInstaller="%AppPath%YondeKoKo"
UpdateName="Yonde Koko"
UpdateCTI=61

[Japanese]
ApplicationName="読んde!!ココ パーソナル"

[ApplicationDescription]
Japanese="スキャナーを使って紙面上の文字をテキストデータに変換できる日本語OCR(文字認識)ソフトウェアです。"
English="This software lets you scan a document and convert the text into data that you can edit with a word processing program. "
French="Ce logiciel vous permet de numériser un document et de convertir le texte en données que vous pouvez modifier à l'aide d'un programme de traitement de texte. "
German="Mit dieser Software können Sie ein Dokument scannen und den Text in Daten konvertieren, die mit einem Textverarbeitungsprogramm verarbeitet werden können."
Dutch="Met deze software kunt u een document scannen en de tekst omzetten in gegevens die u kunt gebruiken in een tekstverwerker."
Italian="Questo software consente di effettuare la scansione di un documento e di convertire il testo in dati modificabili con un programma di elaborazione testo."
Spanish="Este software le permite escanear un documento y convertir el texto en datos que pueda editar con un programa de procesamiento de textos. "
Portuguese="Este software permite-lhe digitalizar um documento e converter o texto em dados que pode editar com um programa de processamento de texto. "
Turkish="Bu yazılım, bir belgeyi taramanızı ve metni, bir kelime işlemcisinde düzenleyebileceğiniz bir veriye dönüştürebilmenizi sağlar. "
Greek="Αυτό το λογισμικό σάς επιτρέπει να σαρώνετε ένα έγγραφο και να μετατρέπετε το κείμενο σε δεδομένα που μπορείτε να επεξεργαστείτε μέσω ενός προγράμματος επεξεργασίας κειμένου."
Slovenian="S to programsko opremo lahko skenirano besedilo spremenite v podatke, ki jih lahko urejate z besedilnimi programi."
Croatian="Ovaj softver Vam omogućava skeniranje dokumenta i pretvorbu teksta u podatke koje možete uređivati putem programa za obradu teksta. "
Macedonian="Софтверот овозможува сканирање документи и претворање текст во податоци што може да се уредуваат со програми за обработување текст. "
Serbian="Ovaj softver omogućava skeniranje dokumenta i pretvaranje teksta u podatke koje možete menjati programom za obradu teksta."
Danish="Denne software giver dig mulighed for at scanne et dokument og konvertere teksten til data, der kan redigeres med et tekstbehandlingsprogram."
Finnish="Tällä ohjelmistolla voit skannata dokumentin ja muuntaa tekstin tekstinkäsittelyohjelmistossa muokattavaksi. "
Norwegian="Med denne programvaren kan du skanne et dokument og konvertere teksten til data, som du kan redigere med et tekstbehandlingsprogram."
Swedish="Med programmet kan du skanna dokument och konvertera text till data som kan redigeras med ordbehandlingsprogram."
Polish="Ten program pozwala skanować dokument i przekształcać tekst na dane, które można edytować w edytorze tekstów."
Czech="Tento software vám umožní naskenovat dokument a převést text na data, které můžete editovat pomocí textového editoru."
Hungarian="Ezzel a szoftverrel szkennelhet dokumentumot, és átalakíthat szöveget olyan adattá, amelyet szövegszerkesztő programmal szerkeszthet."
Slovakian="Tento softvér vám umožní naskenovať dokument a previesť text na dáta, ktoré môžete editovať pomocou textového editora."
Romanian="Acest program vă permite să scanaţi un document şi să convertiţi textul în date editabile cu ajutorul unui program de procesare de text. "
Bulgarian="Този софтуер ви позволява да сканирате и преобразувате текст в данни, които можете да редактирате с текстова програма."
Latvian="Šī programmatūra ļauj skenēt dokumentu un pārveidot tekstu datos, kurus jūs varat rediģēt, izmantojot datu apstrādes programmu."
Lithuanian="Ši įranga leidžia nuskaityti dokumentą ir paversti tekstą duomenimis, kuriuos galite apdoroti teksto redagavimo programa."
Estonian="Selle tarkvaraga saate dokumenti skannida ja teisendada teksti failiks, mida saab tekstiredaktoriga töödelda."
Catalan="Aquest programari permet escanejar un document i convertir el text en dades, les quals es poden editar amb un programa de processament de textos. "
Russian="Это программное обеспечение позволяет вам отсканировать документ и преобразовать текст в данные, которые можно редактировать с помощью программы подготовки текстов."
Ukrainian="Це ПЗ дає змогу сканувати документи й перетворювати їх у формат для їх зміни за допомогою текстового редактора."
Kazakh="Осы бағдарлама сізге құжатты сканерлеп, оны мәтінге ауыстырып, осы ақпаратты мәтін бағдарламада өзгерту мүмкіндік береді."
Arabic="يتيح لك هذا البرنامج مسح مستند ضوئيًا ثم تحويل النص إلى بيانات يمكنك تحريرها بواسطة برنامج معالجة النصوص. "
Farsi=" با این نرم افزار می توانید یك سند را اسكن كرده و متن خود را به داده ای تبدیل كنید كه با استفاده از یك برنامه پردازشگر كلمه قادر به ویرایش آن باشید."
Korean="문서를 스캔하고 텍스트 데이터로 변환하여 워드 프로세싱 프로그램에서 편집할 수 있게 하는 소프트웨어입니다."
Thai="ซอฟต์แวร์นี้ทำให้ท่านสแกนเอกสาร และแปลงข้อความเป็นข้อมูลที่ท่านสามารถแก้ไขได้ด้วยโปรแกรมเวิร์ดโปรเซสซิ่ง"
Chinese="本软件让您可扫描文档，并将文本转换为可使用文字处理程序编辑的数据。"
Taiwan="此軟體可讓您在掃描文件時，將文字轉換成可在文書處理軟體中編輯的資料。 "
HongKong=""
